[
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what was the literacy rate of Bihar?",
        "answer": "61.8 percent",
        "choices": [
            "61.8 percent",
            "58.5 percent",
            "65.3 percent",
            "70.2 percent"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "What was the literacy rate of India as per the Census 2011?",
        "answer": "74.0 percent",
        "choices": [
            "74.0 percent",
            "61.8 percent",
            "65.4 percent",
            "68.7 percent"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which district has highest literacy rate in Bihar?",
        "answer": "Rohtas",
        "choices": [
            "Rohtas",
            "Patna",
            "Purnea",
            "Gopalganj"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which district has lowest literacy rate in Bihar?",
        "answer": "Purnea",
        "choices": [
            "Purnea",
            "Munger",
            "Rohtas",
            "Gopalganj"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what was the male literacy rate in Bihar?",
        "answer": "71.2 percent",
        "choices": [
            "71.2 percent",
            "61.8 percent",
            "74.0 percent",
            "51.5 percent"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what was the female literacy rate in Bihar?",
        "answer": "51.5 percent",
        "choices": [
            "51.5 percent",
            "61.8 percent",
            "74.0 percent",
            "71.2 percent"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "Which state had the highest literacy rate according to Census 2011?",
        "answer": "Kerala",
        "choices": [
            "Kerala",
            "Bihar",
            "Tamil Nadu",
            "Maharashtra"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "Which state had the lowest literacy rate according to Census 2011?",
        "answer": "Bihar",
        "choices": [
            "Bihar",
            "Jharkhand",
            "West Bengal",
            "Assam"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what is the sex-ratio of Bihar?",
        "answer": 918,
        "choices": [
            918,
            943,
            950,
            981
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what is the sex-ratio of India?",
        "answer": 943,
        "choices": [
            943,
            918,
            948,
            952
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which district has the highest sex-ratio in Bihar?",
        "answer": "Gopalganj",
        "choices": [
            "Gopalganj",
            "Munger",
            "Purnea",
            "Patna"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which district has the lowest sex-ratio in Bihar?",
        "answer": "Munger",
        "choices": [
            "Munger",
            "Gopalganj",
            "Sheohar",
            "Kaimur"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what is the population density of Bihar?",
        "answer": "1106 sq km",
        "choices": [
            "1106 sq km",
            "382 sq km",
            "812 sq km",
            "1206 sq km"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what is the population density of India?",
        "answer": "382 sq km",
        "choices": [
            "382 sq km",
            "1106 sq km",
            "812 sq km",
            "1206 sq km"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which district has the highest population density in Bihar?",
        "answer": "Sheohar",
        "choices": [
            "Sheohar",
            "Sheikhpura",
            "Kaimur",
            "Rohtas"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which district has the lowest population density in Bihar?",
        "answer": "Kaimur",
        "choices": [
            "Kaimur",
            "Sheikhpura",
            "Sheohar",
            "Rohtas"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which district has the lowest population in Bihar?",
        "answer": "Sheikhpura",
        "choices": [
            "Sheikhpura",
            "Sheohar",
            "Kaimur",
            "Patna"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which district has the highest population in Bihar?",
        "answer": "Patna",
        "choices": [
            "Patna",
            "Sheohar",
            "Kaimur",
            "Sheikhpura"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "Which State has the highest population according to Census 2011?",
        "answer": "Uttar Pradesh",
        "choices": [
            "Uttar Pradesh",
            "Bihar",
            "Maharashtra",
            "West Bengal"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "Which State has the lowest population according to Census 2011?",
        "answer": "Sikkim",
        "choices": [
            "Sikkim",
            "Manipur",
            "Tripura",
            "Goa"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "Which Union Territory has the lowest population according to Census 2011?",
        "answer": "Lakshadweep",
        "choices": [
            "Lakshadweep",
            "Andmand & Nicobar Islands",
            "Puducherry",
            "Ladakh"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "Which Union Territory has the highest population according to Census 2011?",
        "answer": "Delhi",
        "choices": [
            "Delhi",
            "Ladakh",
            "Jammu & Kashmir",
            "Chandigarh"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which district has the lowest population in India?",
        "answer": "Dibang Valley, Arunachal Pradesh",
        "choices": [
            "Dibang Valley, Arunachal Pradesh",
            "Leh, Ladakh",
            "Mahe, Puducherry",
            "Diu, Daman & Diu"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which district has the highest population in India?",
        "answer": "Thane, Maharashtra",
        "choices": [
            "Thane, Maharashtra",
            "Sheohar, Bihar",
            "Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh",
            "Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "Which State has the highest population density according to Census 2011?",
        "answer": "Bihar",
        "choices": [
            "Bihar",
            "Uttar Pradesh",
            "Mahrashtra",
            "Sikkim"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "Which State has the lowest population density according to Census 2011?",
        "answer": "Arunachal Pradesh",
        "choices": [
            "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "Assam",
            "Sikkim",
            "Goa"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "Which Union Territory has the highest population density according to Census 2011?",
        "answer": "Delhi",
        "choices": [
            "Delhi",
            "Lakshadweep",
            "Andman & Nicobar Islands",
            "Ladakh"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "Which Union Territory has the lowest population density according to Census 2011?",
        "answer": "Andman & Nicobar Islands",
        "choices": [
            "Andman & Nicobar Islands",
            "Lakshadweep",
            "Daman & Diue",
            "Ladakh"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what was the total population of India?",
        "answer": "121 crore",
        "choices": [
            "121 crore",
            "11 crore",
            "110 crore",
            "112 crore"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what was the total population of Bihar?",
        "answer": "10.4 crore",
        "choices": [
            "10.4 crore",
            "14 crore",
            "104 crore",
            "41 crore"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, Bihar’s population is approximately what percent of India’s total population?",
        "answer": "8.6 percent",
        "choices": [
            "8.6 percent",
            "7.2 percent",
            "9.4 percent",
            "10.2 percent"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "In terms of population, what is the rank of Bihar?",
        "answer": "Third",
        "choices": [
            "Third",
            "Second",
            "First ",
            "Fourth"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, the percentage of urban and rural population of Bihar is respectively",
        "answer": "11.3% and 88.7%",
        "choices": [
            "11.3% and 88.7%",
            "13.4% and 86.6%",
            "17.3% and 82.7%",
            "10.2% and 89.8%"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "In terms of urban population, Bihar ranks among the states/union territories of the country?",
        "answer": "12th",
        "choices": [
            "12th",
            "11th",
            "13th",
            "14th"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which is the most populous Scheduled Tribe in Bihar?",
        "answer": "Santhal",
        "choices": [
            "Santhal",
            "Bhil",
            "Gond",
            "Munda"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, which is the most populous Scheduled Tribe in India?",
        "answer": "Bhil",
        "choices": [
            "Bhil",
            "Santhal",
            "Gond",
            "Munda"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what percentage of tribal population lives in India?",
        "answer": "8.6 percent",
        "choices": [
            "8.6 percent",
            "1.3 percent",
            "9.4 percent",
            "7.2 percent"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "Census",
        "question": "According to Census 2011, what percentage of tribal population lives in Bihar?",
        "answer": "1.3 percent",
        "choices": [
            "1.3 percent",
            "8.6 percent",
            "9.4 percent",
            "7.2 percent"
        ]
    }
]